const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '700 − 552 =', answer: '148', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '900 − 233 =', answer: '667', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '300 − 157 =', answer: '143', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '800 − 665 =', answer: '135', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '400 − 147 =', answer: '253', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '600 − 462 =', answer: '138', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '500 − 278 =', answer: '222', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '900 − 432 =', answer: '468', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '800 − 625 =', answer: '175', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '600 − 384 =', answer: '216', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];